{"questions":[{"question":"In Peer Review We...","level":1,"answers":["Identify needed improvements","Certify correctness","Encourage uniformity","All of the above"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":3},{"question":"When does the requirements step gets into the project ?","level":2,"answers":["In the first levels","level after design","before writing the first document","In the development stage"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["client","cloud","soft","all of the mentioned"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"How many values and principles Agile has?","level":1,"answers":["Two","Three","Four","Five"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which of the following is NOT a type of SRS Template?","level":3,"answers":["organized by object","organized by functional hierarchy","organized by version","organized by feature"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"\"A maintenance programmer must have superb debugging skills\"","level":2,"answers":["True","False","Preferred but not obligatory","Not necessary at all"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Which of the following is an Agile role?","level":2,"answers":["Product owner","Manager","Secretary","Lab Worker"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Which of the following is one of the\n formal reviews process?","level":1,"answers":["improvise a session with group of members","post review activities","talking with the manager about sessions","gathering results"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"which of the following is not a maintenance type?","level":3,"answers":["Corrective Maintenance","Continuative Maintenance","Perfective Maintenance","Adaptive Maintenance"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Which of the following is NOT an Architecture pattern?","level":2,"answers":["Layered architecture","Client-Server architecture","Client-Client architecture","Model-View Controller"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":" Is TDD an Agile methodology?","level":1,"answers":["Yes","No","I dont know","we didnt learn about it"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":0},{"question":"What is quality analyst in testing?","level":1,"answers":["quality assurance throughout hardware development life cycle","quality assurance and solving bugs ","applies the principles and practices of software quality assurance","testing hardware issues"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"which of type following is highest degree\n of integration in cloud computing?","level":2,"answers":["Caas","Aaas","Paas","Saas"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":3},{"question":"How do you use QA in Agile?","level":2,"answers":["talk with the manager once in two weeks","Attend daily stand ups","send updates evrey two weeks","in agile we work seperately"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What system aspects are included in architectural design decisions?","level":3,"answers":["Behavior & Interaction","Interaction & Non-functional properties","Non-functional properties & Interaction & Behavior & Structure","Non-functional properties"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which of the following are types of reviews?","level":1,"answers":["A-Formal Reviews","B-Peer Reviews","C-Unformal Reviews ","D- A & B"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":3},{"question":"g","level":2,"answers":["g","d","s","a"],"team":"Rabbit","correct_ans":1}]}